A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia Field Office Files FA643
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1950-1975 (Bulk: 1963-1975); 1963-1975; VIII
  - English Language Program, 1970-1973 (Box 24)
  - Gross Domestic Product Reports (retirement plan), 1970 (Box 24)
  - Haradh Project -- Bedouin Settlement, 1969-1972 (Box 24)
  - Illiteracy Eradication and Adult Education, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1964-1969 (Box 25)
  - Institute of Public Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
  - Law and Development, 1967-1973 (Box 25)
  - Manpower Program, 1963-1974 (Box 25)
  - Material Management, 1970-1972 (Box 25)
  - Ministry of Education, 1971-1974 (Box 25)
  - Ministry of Education -- Administrative Training, 1973-1975 (Box 25)
  - Ministry of Finance and National Economy, 1964-1967 (Box 25)
  - Organization and Management, 1964-1972 (Box 25)
  - Organizational Charts -- Saudi Arabia -- Government, 1964-1971 (Box 25)
  - Pay and Classification, 1965-1973 (Box 25)
  - Pension Fund, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Personnel Organization, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
  - Public Management Review, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
  - Public Works, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
  - Revenue Administration, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Revenue Correspondence and Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 25)
  - Riyadh Schools and Ford Foundation Assistance, 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Riyadh University, 1970-1974 (Box 25)
  - Saudi Arabia General Correspondence Files, 1950-1958 (Box 25)
  - Saudi Arabia -- General Files, 1960-1969 (Box 26)
  - Saudi Arabian Economic Plan -- Draft (report scanned and separated - located in reports collection), 1965 (Box 26)
  - School Administrators Program, 1971-1973 (Box 26)
  - Supply Management, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Training -- General Files, 1962-1971 (Box 26)
  - Vocational Training and Education, 1964-1965 (Box 26)
- Royal Decrees and Regulations, 1952-1972; IX
  - Directory of Saudi Royal Family and Government Officials, 1964 (Box 27)
  - Agricultural Bank, 1962-1965 (Box 27)
  - Agriculture, 1961-1966 (Box 27)
  - Central Planning Organization, 1964 (Box 27)
  - Communications (1/2), 1953-1966 (Box 27)
  - Communications (2/2), 1953-1966 (Box 27)
  - Council of Ministers, 1954-1965 (Box 27)
  - Education, 1965-1967 (Box 27)
  - Education, 1970-1972 (Box 27)
  - Finance (1/2), 1956-1971 (Box 27)
  - Finance (2/2), 1956-1971 (Box 27)
  - Institute of Public Administration (IPA), 1962-1967 (Box 27)
  - Petroleum, 1963-1966 (Box 27)
  - Sharia'h Court System, 1952-1957 (Box 27)
  - Social Affairs, 1965-1969 (Box 27)
- Film, X
  - One the Move: Careers in Transportation, undated (Box 28, Reel AV 1992)
    Separated Materials
    Separated to Ford Foundation Film collection.
    Other Finding Aids
    See Ford Foundation film AV 1992 here:
    FA466 Film collection - AV 1992
  - Welcome to the Working Worlds, undated (Box 28, Reel AV 2008)
    See Ford Foundation film AV 2008 here:
    FA466 Film collection - AV 2008
  - Career Education, undated (Box 28, Reel AV 2007)
    See Ford Foundation film AV 2007 here:
    FA466 Film collection - AV 2007